# **DANIEL SHIN**

## SOFTWARE ENGINEER

## **SUMMARY**

I am a software enthusiast with thorough experience in both server-side and client-side technologies. I have worked in various projects from developing web app UIs to integrating multiple APIs to deploying applications on cloud infrastructure.

### **SKILLS**

**LANGUAGES:** Python, JavaScript, Ruby **FRAMEWORKS:** Django, React, Rails **DATABASES:** PostgreSQL, PL/SQL, MySQL

INFRASTRUCTURE: Google Cloud Platform, Kubernetes, Docker

## **EMPLOYMENT**

### OnTheRivt / Pocket Outdoor Media

Software Engineer

Aug. 2019 to Current

- Developed central, multi-site API from scratch with several high-impact integration points in Python / Django
- Integrations include but not limited to: authentication, content ingestion, payments and tax processing, email services, third-party partner APIs
- Deployed to GCP environments with local Kubernetes scripts

**Helix** · Denver

Software Enginer II

Mar. 2018 to Current

- Lead engineer for high-priority, multi-party integration API in Python / Django
- Deployed to GCP environments with local Kubernetes scripts
- Developed integration services in partners' codebase in Python / Web2Py
- Developed UI changes in Helix's main online store in React / Redux

#### **Humancode**. Inc · Denver

Software Enginer

Apr. 2017 to Mar. 2018

- Developed API and integration services in Python / Django
- Served up Intercom CRM and integrated customer support services
- Complete web app development in React / Redux
- Developed a handful of mobile features in Swift

## **Quorum, Inc.** · Houston

Senior Consultant

June 2013 to Apr. 2016

- Ran per-client based Oracle and SQL Server data conversions
- Implemented custom ArcGIS environments
- Developed custom SQL reports for business users

## **EDUCATION**

University of Texas at Austin

Economics Psychology May, 2013

Turing School of Software & Design

**Backend Engineering** 

March, 2017